Guide to the Herman Miles Somers Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- WRITINGS, 1936-1978; Series IV; 3' (9 boxes)
  - Monographs
    - "Roles of the Public and Private Sectors in Financing and Delivery of Health Care, Proceedings, Third International Conference, International Federation of Volunteer Health Insurance Funds: speech text, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - "The Role of the Private Sector in the U.S.A., Proceedings, Anglo-American Conference on Medical Care: tear sheets, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Disease by Disease Toward National Health Insurance, with Anne R. Somers and others, National Academy of Sciences, Institute of Medicine: monograph, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Health and Health Care: Policies in Perspective, with Anne R. Somers
      - Correspondence with John Wiley & Sons, 1973-1977 (Box 32, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, 1975, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 26)
      - Draft, part I, chapters II-V, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 27)
      - Draft, part II, chapters II-VII, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 28)
      - Draft, part II, chapters VIII-X, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 29)
      - Draft, part III, chapters II-VI, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 30)
      - Draft, part III, chapters VI-IX, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence, travel vouchers and notes, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 32)
      - Draft, Preface through part II, chapter IV, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 33)
      - Draft, part II, chapter V through part III, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 34)
      - Draft, part III, chapter VIII through chapter XI, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 35)
      - Draft, part III, chapter XI through part IV, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - "Certificate-of-Need Regulation: The Case of New Jersey," with Anne R. Somers, Regionalization and Health Policy: tear sheet, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - "Changing Lifestyles: Political and Economic Issues," The Fourth International Seminar: Health Education and Its Practice in Community Health Care: speech text, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Speeches & Shorter Writings
    - 1938-1941, 1945-1957 (Box 35, Folder 39-42)
    - 1958 (Box 35, Folder 43)
      See also: box 32, folder 11
    - 1959-1962 May (Box 35, Folder 44-46)
    - 1962 June-Dec, 1964 February-Dec, 1965-1967 (Box 36, Folder 47-53)
    - 1968-1971 January-Oct, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 54-60)
    - 1974-1977 (Box 38, Folder 61-67)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 68-69)
    - Undated speeches (Box 39, Folder 70)
    - Unidentified speeches (Box 39, Folder 71)